字幕來源：電波字幕組
翻校人員：暗夜光子  怪查理
后期：Lee.
"貝琪"
'Betsy'
"不"
'No!'
小心  他就在你身后
Watch out! He's right behind you!
擋住視線了
Hey! Damn it front.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
"我來抓你了  貝琪"
'I'm coming to get you Betsy.'
快跑啊  貝琪  快跑
Run Betsy! Run!
拜托  她根本不可能逃出吸血鬼的掌心
Come on! There is no way she can outrun a vampire.
別聽她的貝琪  你可以的
Don't listen to her Betsy, you can do it.
不要放棄
Don't give up.
到了嗎
Are we there yet?
還有幾個小時  邦妮
No for a few more hours Bonnie.
你可以再睡一會
You can go back to sleep.
'救命  請開門'
'Help! Open the door!'
'沒人能幫你了貝琪'
'No one can help you now Betsy.'
無聊
Boring.
有點耐心
Patience.
好看的恐怖片都是慢慢推進的
All great horror film starts slowly.
你看  他們設計
You see,they design...
'求你了  讓我進去'
'Please, let me in!'
想辦法  貝琪  快想辦法
Tactics, Betsy, tactics.
找個能防衛自己的工具
Look for something to defend yourself with.
總算
There we go.
技術上來說那個一點用都沒有
Oh, technically that would be useless.
所有人都知道用木棍直插心臟
Everybody knows a wooden stake through the heart
是殺死吸血鬼的唯一方式
is the only way to kill a vampire.
啊
Ahhh!
哈哈  一只小貓  經典的障眼法
Haha, only a kitty cat, classic misdirection.
一只貓
A cat?!
拜托  這一點都不嚇人
Come on guys, this isn't scary.
救命  把我救出去
Help! Get me out of here!
杰西  我們得把她救出來
Jessie, we have to get her out.
杰西  杰西  能聽見嗎
Jessie, Jessie, can you hear me?
大家  數到三
Ok, everyone, on three.
一  二  三
One, two, three!
杰西  杰西
Jessie? Jessie!
杰西怎么了
What's the matter with Jessie?
她被遺棄在一只盒子里好幾年
She was abandoned in a box for years.
我沒法  我沒法逃出去
I couldn't...I couldn't find a way out.
媽媽  我能帶上我的玩具嗎
Mum, can I bring my toys?
路邊的汽車旅館是恐怖片中最常見的場景之一
The roadside motel is one of the most common road cons for a horror film.
偏僻  無人  普通
Remote, isolated, ordinary,
給觀眾營造一種毫不可疑的舒心環境
a comforting environment to a latest suspicion of audience.
我猜她馬上
I expect they'll be asking
就要向旅館老板借電話
the inn keeper to use the telephone any minute now.
'我能借電話用一下嗎'
'Would it be ok if I use your phone?'
'我們的輪胎漏氣了'
'Our car is a flat.'
時間恰好
Right on cue.
沒事的杰西  你很安全
It's ok Jessie, you'll be safe now.
很快我們就會重新上路了
We'll be back on the road before you know it.
有什么最新消息  特里克
What's the latest, Trixie?
她還在和拖車公司通話
She's still on the phone with the tolltruck company.
'早上六點  這是你最早能到這的時間嗎'
'6 a.m.? That's the earliest you can get here?'
六點
意味著我們要在這里待一晚上嗎
You mean we have to stay here all night?
砰  砰  砰
Bom bom bom!
我不在乎我們在哪
I don't care where we are,
只要我不獨自困在那個盒子里
as long as I'm not stuck alone in that box.
請在旅客本上簽字
You think you could just sign here on the guest book?
我去幫你刷卡
and I'll leave to see the major credit card for the incidentals.
讓我們看看  你住七號房間吧
Ok, let's see here. I'm gonna put you in room 7.
我們這里有個說法
You know we have a little saying around here.
在好夢旅館  好夢伴隨你
At the Sleep-Well Motel, you're gonna sleep well.
看起來她們睡著了
Well, it looks like they are asleep.
終于
Finally!
土豆頭  你要去哪
Potato Head, where are you going?
我們在旅館  我只是想看看這里的便利設施
We're at a motel, I just wanna check out the amenities.
就是免費的東西啦
You know, the free stuff.
小肥皂  浴帽  洗發露  護發素
Little soaps, shower caps, shampoo, conditioner.
我是你的話就不會出去
Oh, I wouldn't go out there if I were you.
第一個離開的總是遇到麻煩
The first leave usually gets it.
土豆頭  不要離開行李箱
Oh, Potato Head, don't leave the bag.
汽車旅館是玩具最容易走丟的地方
A motel is one of the easiest places for a toy to get lost.
別亂擔心了
Shut your worry hole.
沒人會走丟的
Nobody's gonna get lost.
況且  我答應艾瑪要給她帶點好東西回去
Besides, I promised Emma that I bring her back something nice.
等等  你們又要去哪
Wait, where are you guys going?
我們只是去看看免費的東西
We're just gonna check out the free stuff.
如果土豆頭真的遇到麻煩  我可不想錯過好戲
And if something does happen to the Potato, I wouldn't want to miss it.
拜托  伙計們  待在行李箱里好嗎
Oh come on guys! Let's all just stay in the bag.
巴茲  我去找那些家伙  你找土豆頭
Oh Buzz, I'll grab those guys, you get Potato head.
好的
Got it.
不  等等  不要走
No wait! Don't go!
不要擔心杰西  馬上回來
Don't worry Jessie, I'll be right back!
巴茲
Buzz!
伙計們  你們在哪
Guys guys! Where are you?
杰西  怎么了  你還好嗎
Jessie, what's wrong? Are you ok?
巴茲  大伙呢
Buzz, where is everybody?
不要擔心  我們都在這里
Not to worry, we're all right here.
看  伍迪  褲子刺猬  特里克  雷克斯
See, there's Woody, Pricklepants, Trixie, Rex,
等等  土豆頭在哪
Wait, where is Potato head?
好戲開始
And so it begins.
褲子刺猬  不要幫倒忙
Pricklepants, you're not helping.
我只是想說這種恐怖片中
I'm just saying it's quite common in these types of movies
某個毫無疑心的角色走著走著消失了很正常
for one unsuspecting character to wander off and vanish.
好吧  他不可能憑空消失
Well, he couldn't have just disappeared.
也許這地方鬧鬼
Maybe this place is haunted.
什么  鬧鬼
What? It's haunted?
當然不是  大家都知道世界上沒有鬼
Of course not. Everybody knows ghosts aren't real.
實際上  根據我的互聯網研究
Actually, according to my internet research...
不可能
Highly unlikely.
一定有一個合理的解釋
There has to be a rational explanation.
我們分成兩人一組
We need break into groups of two.
看好你的搭檔
Everyone keep an eye on your partner.
任何異常  尖叫一聲
Anything goes wrong, give a yell.
啊
Ahhh!
我踩到什么東西了
Ew, I stepped in something.
惡心
Ew!
等一下
Wait a minute.
嗯
Hmm...
這是什么
What is it?
惡心
Disgusting.
如果這里是電影
Were...Were this a movie,
一定是在怪獸變形的時候掉下的
I'd say it was sliding from the creature's metamorphosis.
好吧  不管是什么
Yeah, well, whatever it is,
土豆頭踩到了
Potato Head managed to step in it,
留下了一串腳印
leaving behind a trailer of footprints,
我們跟著腳印  應該就能找到他
If we follow it, should lead us right to it.
伙計們
Hey guys!
等等  特里克  不要
No wait! Trixie! Don't!
特里克
Trixie!
Trixie?
土豆頭
Potato Head?
這就是黑暗之塔
And this would be the turrical.
每部電影都有
Every movie has one, you know.
一旦英雄進去  再也沒有退路
Once the hero enter, there's no turning back.
雷克斯  趕快
Rex, hurry up!
來了
Coming!
現在我們只需找到一條下去的路
Now we just need to find a way down.
啊
Ahhh!
還真下來了
Well, that did the job.
抱歉
Sorry.
大家都還好嗎
Is everyone ok?
啊
Ahh!
那里
That way.
所有人  緊靠一起
Alright everybody, stay close.
接下來會怎樣
So, what happens now?
大家會被拆散
Well, this would be the part
然后一個接一個被抓
where the characters get separated and then picked off one by one.
然后呢
Then what happens next?
啊
Ahhh!
褲子刺猬在哪
Where is Pricklepants?
他剛剛還站在這里
He was standing right here just a moment ago.
我們要怎么辦
What are we gonna do now?
他是唯一知道接下來會發生什么的人
He was the only one who knew what the heck is going on!
啊啊啊啊
Ahhhhhh!
等等  等等  聽
Wait, wait, listen.
我覺得我們甩掉它了
I think we lost it.
在那
It's over there!
什么
What?
這里
Over here.
我看到了  它正在盯著我們看
I think I can see it, it's staring right at us.
是土豆頭的手臂
It's Potato Head's arm.
等一下  他貌似想告訴我們什么
Wait a minute, it looks like it's trying to tell us something.
到底是什么
What is it, little buddy?
他好像在用某種手勢
I think he's using some kind of hand signals.
是數字一
It's the number one.
不  一個單詞
No, one letter.
一個音節
One syllable?
很久以前
Uh, once upon a time.
一加一等于一
Uh, one plus one is one.
也許他是指上面
I think maybe it's pointing up?
-上面  -對
-Up! -Yeah!
當然
Of course!
把手遞給我
Pass me the hand, will you?
接下來怎么辦
What now?
出門  右拐
Out the door and to the right?
什么  你確定嗎
What? Are you sure?
我覺得指的是左邊
The hand looks like it's pointing left to me.
啊
Huh?
這邊
Over here.
什么
What?
看這邊
Look over here.
有人嗎  有人嗎
Hello? Hello?
伙計們  等一下
Hey, guys. Wait up!
伍迪  巴茲
Woody! Buzz!
噓  安靜士兵  你會把他們引過來的
Shhh! Quite soldier, you'll lead them right to us.
玩具在這里太危險
This place isn't safe for toys.
步兵卡爾要把手移開了
Combat Carl's gonna take his hand away now.
你叫  我們都完蛋
You yell, we're done for.
明白嗎
Got it?
步兵卡爾經歷過好多
Combat Carl's seen things,
可怕的事情
horrible things.
步兵卡爾學會了永不停止
Combat Carl's learned, you gotta keep moving,
否則他們會找到你
or else they'll find you.
你是步兵卡爾嗎
Are you Combat Carl?
讓步兵卡爾堅持到現在的唯一原因
The only thing that's kept Combat Carl going is
他想也許他還能再見一次他的主人比利
the thought he might see his owner Billy just one more time.
你最好現在就回去
You better turn back now,
否則你再也見不到你的主人
or you'll never see your owner again.
但我得找到我的朋友
But I need to find my friends.
這就是你去找你朋友的下場
This is what happens when you try to find your friends.
噓  聽到了嗎
Shhh. Did you hear that?
他找到我們了  我們被困住了
He found us, we are trapped.
不  步兵卡爾從不放棄
No, Combat Carl never gives up,
步兵卡爾總能想到辦法
Combat Carl finds a way.
我們得走了  準備好了嗎
We gotta move. You ready?
什么  不
What? No!
數到三
We're going on three.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
抓緊我
Grab my arm.
卡爾  等等  卡爾
Carl, wait, Carl!
不要管步兵卡爾  快逃
Forget about Combat Carl, just go!
啊
Ahhhh!
喂
Hey!
放開我  你這個大壞蛋
Let me go! You big vomit!
立刻放開我
Let me go instant!
謝謝  很有趣
Thank you, well, it's been fun.
麻煩來了
看起來挺舊的  應該值點錢
Hmm, looks old, probably worth something.
干得好  瓊斯先生
Excellent find, Mr. Jones.
他走了
He's gone.
安全
All clear.
杰西
Jessie!
巴茲
Buzz
你沒事真是太好了
I'm so glad you're safe.
牛仔女  你總算安然無恙地找到這里  真是不錯
Nice to see you made it here in one piece, cowgirl.
卡爾
Carl!
讓我來給你介紹一下
Combat Carl would like to introduce you
步兵卡爾三分之一大小模型  小步兵卡爾
to his one third skill counterpart, Combat Carl Junior.
小姐  抱歉打擾了你歡聚的喜悅  我們現在時間緊張
Ma'am sorry to break up the party, but we're on a tight schedule.
帕克提爾  到你上了
Pocketeer, you're up!
口袋出擊
Pockets away!
樂高兔子  上
Lego bunny, go!
有看到那個人或者那只蜥蜴嗎
Any sign of our guy or the lizard?
沒有  這里仍然安全
No sir. Area is still clear.
老時鐘
Hey, old timer.
時間來得及嗎
How we doing.
讓我看看
Well, sir.
他已經離開了19秒
He's been gone for nineteen seconds.
經理羅恩隨時都可能回來
Ron the manager could come back any minute.
好  就讓我再試一試
OK, let's try this again.
第三次一定能成功
Third time's the charm.
你辦得到
You can do it, Junior.
穩住  別緊張
Steady. Take it easy now.
差一點就成功了
Almost got it！
哦不
Oh-no!
糟糕
Sassafras!
那是最后一個了
That was the last one!
意味著  我是  下一個
That means, I'm next!
你們看不到嗎  我是牢固四俠的最后一個
Don't you see, I'm the last of the Fastener Four.
看  先是拉鏈男人  再是卡扣  然后是駭速快手
Look, Zipper man! Snaps! Speed lacer!
我是下一個
I'm next!
下一個就是我
我是
I'm...
冷靜下來  伙計
Keep it together man!
我們會找到出路的
We will find a way out!
我們是會找到出路的  裝在盒子里罷了
We will get out all right, in boxes.
啥
What!
杰西  沒人會被裝進盒子里
Jessie, nobody is getting boxed up.
我們會一起離開的
We're leaving together.
您有一筆銷售
You have a sale.
佩斯貓  你看到什么了
Pez cat, what do you see!
啊嗚  看不太清誒
Ah-u, it's hard to make out.
不過看起來像是一個  牛仔
But it looks like a cowboy.
我們看看下一個賣掉的是什么
let's see what's next to go.
什么  2000塊
What! 2000 dollars!
吼吼吼  瓊斯  瓊斯
Hohoho, Jones Jones.
你不會相信的
You're not gonna believe this.
旅途愉快  牛仔安迪
Happy trails, cowboy Andy.
就像搶嬰兒的糖果一樣容易
Like taking candy from a baby.
他會想辦法逃出來的  伍迪
He'll be able to get out, Woody.
我也不知道
I have no foggist idea.
一開始就是個經典的恐怖電影
What starts out is a classic horror film has turned
結果變成了悲劇
into something more of a tragedy.
我不敢相信  我們將再也見不到邦妮了
I can't believe we're never gonna see Bonnie again.
步兵卡爾想再見一次比利
Combat Carl would have liked to see Billy just one more time.
卡爾  我們會找到辦法的
We'll find a way, Carl.
會找到辦法的
We'll find a way.
戰士們  你們最好快點
Hey, you better hurry Soldier.
聽起來  修理人員隨時可能出現哦
Sound fixing arrives in any minute now.
您有一筆銷售
You have a sale.
大家快回到原位
People, back to your position.
好極了  來了  大生意
All right. Come on, Big money.
這次輪到誰了
Who is it this time?
好  我來看看  我在看
OK, I'm looking, I'm looking.
天啊  他站起來了
Oh my god, he's getting up.
瓊斯  瓊斯  我們找到另一個大金礦了
Jonesy, Jonesy, we got another gold mine.
看起來  該你上路了
Looks like you get to go on a little trip.
是你給加油站打電話  說有輪胎要修理的吧
Yeah, you got a gas for the flat-tire that needs fixing.
是的  我帶你去
Absolutely. Come on, I'll show you the way.
好了  他走了
OK, he's gone!
沒用的  我不夠高
It's no use. I'm not tall enough.
我去找伍迪
I'll go get Woody.
我們一起就可以夠得著把手了
Together we will be able to reach the handle.
好計劃  杰西
Good plan, Jessie.
有人到門口了
Ahh! Someone's at the door.
放在那里  柜臺上的都送走
Stack there, and the ones on the counter all go too.
好的
OKAY.
看來我得跑兩趟了
Looks I'm gonna have to take two trips.
伍迪
Ah Woody!
好吧  我們需要B計劃
Alright, we need a plan B.
大家都想想
Put on your thinking caps, people.
我想到了
I got it.
她可以闖進送貨車里
She can make a break through the delivery truck.
這可行不通
It's what daylight.
況且  她也趕不上啊
Besides, she will never make it in time.
我該怎么辦
What do I do?
現在我們都將會被關進盒子里
Now, we're all gonna end up in a box.
等等  這就對了
Wait, that's it.
杰西  再說一遍
Jessie say that again.
說什么
Say what?
說我們最終都會被關進盒子里
That we're all gonna end up in boxes?
不是我們  是你
Not us, you.
你要進到盒子里
You're gonna get in the box.
什么
What?
幾分鐘后  那個運貨小姐
Listen, in a few minutes, the delivery lady
就回來拿剩下的幾個盒子
is gonna come back through that door and take the other boxes.
你就混在其中
And you are gonna be in one of them.
這是你救伍迪唯一的辦法
It's the only way to free Woody.
不行  我不行  我辦不到
No, no way. I can't. I can't do that.
我不能進到盒子里  我不能
I can't get in a box. I can't!
一定有其他的辦法
There's gotta be another way.
這是唯一的辦法
This is the way.
你得振作起來  戰士
You better snap out of it, soilder.
我們現在時間緊迫  你是我們唯一的希望
We're running out of time. And you are the only chance we've got.
不  我不行的
No! I can't.
杰西  聽我說  想想你的特訓
Jessie, Listen to me. Remember your training.
但是我沒特訓過
But I don't have any training.
啥  那算了
What, forget about that!
當步兵卡爾遭遇危機  他對自己說
When Combat Carl get stuck in a jam, he says to himself:
步兵卡爾永不放棄
Combat Carl never gives up!
步兵卡爾能想到辦法
Combat Carl finds a way!
現在跟我說
Now say it!
步兵卡爾永不放棄
Combat Carl never gives up!
你不是步兵卡爾
You're not Combat Carl!
杰西永不放棄
Jessie never gives up!
杰西能想到辦法
Jessie finds a way!
我聽不見
I can't hear you.
杰西永不放棄
Jessie never gives up!
杰西能想到辦法
Jessie finds a way!
耶
Yeah!
還有一件事
One more thing!
小聲點
Keep it down.
好吧
I'll try.
醒醒  你自由了
Wake up, you're free.
誰敢召喚Transt
Who dares summon Transtron?
我要用這個盒子
I need to use this box.
Transt自由了
Transtron free?
是  過來  幫我個忙
Yes, right here, give me your hand.
我怎么報答你呢
Er...How can I ever repay you?
把我封起來
Seal me in.
額
Er.
好
OK.
到你了
You're up.
等等  停手  別封住
Wait, wait, don't tape it.
這樣我就出不來了
I won't be able to get out.
關上盒子  把那個盒子放在我上面
Just close the flaps and put that box on the top of it,
堆起來就好
it'll give it shut.
你確定
Are you sure about this?
不  不確定
No. Not really.
我們星球的神靈一定會讓你永垂不朽的
My globe tron's ghost you shall be remembered,
好吧
All right.
變身  分離
Put the tron. Seperate.
還有其他人
Anything else?
計劃貌似有效
Well, the plan seems to be working.
到目前為止都很好
So far so good.
又忘記封盒子了
Oh forgot to tape again.
什么  不  不
What! No no.
她被封住了
She got sealed in.
沒戲了  我們永遠都出不去了
That's it. We're never gonna get out of here.
杰西永不放棄
Jessie never gives up!
杰西能想到辦法
Jessie finds a way!
問題解決  您隨時可走
You're good to go.
太謝謝了
Thank you so much.
邦妮  你的包包別忘了  我們馬上就要走了
Don't forget your bag Bonnie. We're leaving in two minutes.
不好意思  借過
Excuse me, coming through.
杰西永不放棄
Jessie never gives up!
杰西能想到辦法
Jessie finds a way!
杰西永不放棄
Jessie never gives up!
杰西能想到辦法
Jessie finds a way!
杰西永不放棄
Jessie never gives up!
杰西能想到辦法
Jessie finds a way!
杰西永不放棄
Jessie never gives up!
杰西能想法辦法
Jessie finds a way!
杰西想到辦法了
伍迪  伍迪
Woody? Woody?
杰西  杰西  我在這里
Jessie, Jessie, over here.
都過去好一會了
It's been a while.
我想她回不來了
I don't think she's coming back.
耐心點  電影里不是總說  計謀成功總是欲揚先抑
Patience. Cinematics strategetic always duck.
焦躁小短褲  生活不是電影  他們不會再回來了
Panic pants, life ain't a movie, they're never coming back.
看  他們回來了
Look, they are coming back.
要退房嗎  希望你在這里過得不錯
Checking out? Hope you enjoy your stay.
的確不錯  謝謝
We did, thanks.
杰西  我們走
Come on Jessie, let's move.
媽媽  我們要去外婆家了嗎
Mama, are we going to Grandma's now?
馬上就走  寶貝兒
Any minute, honey.
邦妮
Bonnie.
好  現在站在我肩上  然后我
OK now, climb on my shoulders and then...
杰西  杰西
Jessie, Jessie.
天啊  她在做什么
God, what is she doing?
她直沖向門簾了
She's heading straight for the curtain.
這不是計劃的一部分啊
That's not part of the plan.
杰西
Jessie.
加油
Come on.
我的手
My hand.
看  我早告訴過你吧
See, told you.
好啊
Perfect.
我看不下去了
I can't look.
來抓我啊
Come and get it.
感謝您與好夢旅館共度美好時光
Thanks for staying with us, this is the Sleep-Well.
我的玩具誒
My toys.
不不不  小女孩
No no no, little girl.
那個區域只能員工進入
That area is for employees only.
嘿
Hey!
我不能讓你待在這兒
I can't have you back here.
那些都是我女兒的玩具嗎
Are those my daughter's toys?
杰西
Jessie.
這些  可能是她的
Those are... they might be hers.
只是個誤會而已
It's just a mistake.
知道嗎  我應該報警
You know I really should call the police.
報警  沒必要牽涉到警方
The police? Come on, there's no need to involve the authority.
走吧  邦妮  我們走了
Come on, Bonnie, let's go, we're leaving.
你不考慮賣掉它們嗎
Would you consider selling them, tell you what.
牛仔我出100塊
I'll give you 100 dollars for the cowboy.
你要多少  200
What do you want? 200?
結局了  我們又回到了起點
The epilog! We're back to the location where it all began.
從沒想過我會想念后車廂
Never thought I'd miss the trunk.
你做到了  杰西  你拯救了大家
You did it. Jessie, you saved us all.
杰西沒放棄
Jessie didn't give up!
杰西想到了辦法
Jessie found a way!
好吧  伍迪想說的是  謝謝
Well, Woody wants to say, thanks.
土豆頭  你們看到土豆頭嗎
Potato head, have you seen Potato head?
啥  不
What, no.
天啊  看來怪物轉身回來奪走最終的受害者
Oh, dear. It seems the monster has returned to claim one final victim.
他好著呢  在那兒呢
No, he hasn't. He's right over there.
你回來真是太好了  寶貝兒
Oh, I'm so glad to have you back, baby.
我們以后再也不分離
We are never gonna get saperated again.
真是的
Ahh, nuts.
大家歡聲笑語  我得說陰霾已經離去
Group laughter, I shall say now the worst is behind us
電影也該結束了
and the movie is just about to over.
這就結束了
So, this is the ending?
是的  我說  都到了出演員表的時候
Yes, I'd say everyone in the credits about now.
運輸車到了
Transport has arrived.
聽到貓咪發話了  我們走
You heard the cat, let's move.
謝謝你  伙計
Thanks buddy.
下一站  比利的家
Next stop, Billy's house.
瓊斯
Mr.Jones!
給你  伙計
Here you go, buddy.
歡迎來到好夢旅館  有什么我能
Welcome to the Sleep-Well, How may I...
你是這里的經理嗎
Are you the manager?
我  不  我不是
Me? No, I'm not the manager.
那啥  我去叫他來
I'll tell you what. I'll go get him for you.
早就告訴過你  不要把鑰匙留在車里
Told you not to leave the keys in the car.
嫌犯逃跑
We got a runner.